ILGWU Legal Department Records 5780/081
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- United States of America vs. Interstate Dress Carriers. Minutes of trial., 1980 (Box 34, Folder 8b)
  4/28/80. 1 bound volume.
- United States of America vs. Interstate Dress Carriers. Minutes of trial., 1980 (Box 34, Folder 8c)
  4/29/80. 1 bound volume.
- United States of America vs. Interstate Dress Carriers. Minutes of trial., 1980 (Box 34, Folder 8d)
  4/30/80. 1 bound volume.
- United States of America vs. Interstate Dress Carriers. Minutes of trial., 1980 (Box 34, Folder 8e)
  5/1/80. 1 bound volume.
- United States of America vs. Interstate Dress Carriers. Minutes of trial., 1980 (Box 34, Folder 8f)
  5/2/80. 1 bound volume.
- United States of America vs. Interstate Dress Carriers. Minutes of trial., 1980 (Box 34, Folder 8g)
  5/5/80. 1 bound volume.
- B. Case Summaries (Box 34, Folder 8h)
  Summaries of important cases composed of excerpts from reports of the Legal Department to the General Executive Board.
- Summaries of important cases from Legal Department reports to GEB. (Box 34, Folder 9)
  Includes: Baxley vs. Staub; Blouse Anti-Trust; Federal Trade Commission (California Sportswear); Federation of Union Representatives (FOUR); Hazantown; Judy Bond; Kellwood (Little Rock);; Leonard Workman; Rosario vs. Dolgen, Local 10 and ILGWU
- C. Incomplete Case Files (Box 34, Folder 9a)
  Miscellaneous cases with little or no detail.
- American Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, Inc., et al. vs. Merchants' Ladies Garment Association, Inc., et al. (Box 34, Folder 10)
  Luigi Antonini vs. Louis Hyman, et al.; Joseph Burr vs. United States of America.; Carson Pirie Scott and Company vs. ILGWU, White Goods Workers' Union Local 76, Morris Bialis, Samuel Glassman, Abraham Plotkin, and others.
- Central Cotton Garment Manufacturers Association vs. ILGWU, et al. (Box 34, Folder 11)
- D. Contract Histories (Box 35)
  Correspondence and negotiations related to particularly critical agreements.
- Dressmakers Joint Council and W.T. Grant Company. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Dressmakers Joint Council and W.T. Grant Company. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 35, Folder 2)
- David Dubinsky and Phillip Kapp vs. Blue Dale Dress Company, Inc., and Bertha Fishman, and Gertrude Fishman. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  David Dubinsky and Phillip Kapp vs. Champion Trucking Company, Inc.
- Federal Trade Commission in the Matter of: National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board, et al. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Federal Trade Commission in the Matter of: National Coat and Suit Industry Recovery Board, et al. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Joseph Feller and Sigmund Feller vs. Local 144, ILGWU, et al. (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Independent Association of Women's Manufacturers, Inc., et al. vs. ILGWU, et al.. (Box 35, Folder 6a)
  2 bound volumes.
- Industrial Council of Cloak, Suit and Skirt Manufacturers, Inc., Merchants' Ladies Garment Association, Inc., and Infants' and Children's Coat Association, Inc. vs. Joint Board of Cloak, Suit, Skirt and Reefer Makers' Union and ILGWU. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  Internal Revenue Service.
- Levine, et al. vs. Greenfield-Roffer Corporation. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  Lora Lee Dress Company, Inc. vs. ILGWU, et al.; Nathaniel M. Minkoff vs. Jaunty Junior Inc.; Nathaniel M. Minkoff vs. Scranton Frocks, Inc., Richard Frocks, Inc., and Sherri Frocks, Inc.
- Nathaniel M. Minkoff vs. Scranton Frocks, Inc., Richard Frocks, Inc., and Sherri Frocks, Inc. (Box 35, Folder 9)
- National Dress Manufacturers Association, Inc. vs. United Association of Dress Manufacturers, Inc. (Box 35, Folder 10)
  National Labor Relations Board vs. Dressmakers Joint Council, ILGWU.; Leonard Pace, et al. vs. American Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association, Inc., et al.; Real Silk Hosiery Mills, Inc., Lingerie Department, and ILGWU, Local 277.
- Emily Scardaccione vs. Julius Hochman, et al. (Box 35, Folder 11)
- Dress and Waist Manufacturers' Association vs. ILGWU. (Box 35, Folder 11a)
- Schlesinger vs. Leo Finkenberg, Inc. (Box 35, Folder 12)
  Benjamin Schlesinger and Antonio Crivello vs. Lady Rejane, Inc.; Benjamin Schlesinger, et al. vs. Philip Quinto.
- Benjamin Schlesinger, et al. vs. Philip Quinto. (Box 35, Folder 13)
- Benjamin Schlesinger, et al. vs. Joseph Stein. (Box 35, Folder 14)
  Max M. Schwartz vs. ILGWU, et al.; United States of America vs. Cloak and Suit Trucking Association, Inc., et al.
- Blouse contract negotiations., 1958-1962 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  11/58-2/62.
- Bobbie Brooks. 1976 negotiations. [folder 1 of 3], 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  6/76-8/77. Includes agreements for Vandalia, Charleston, Colebrook, Coosa River, Coamo, Butler, and Bellaire subsidiaries; and Brooks Transportation, Cleveland Cutting Center, and Solon/Kelley Distribution Center.
- Bobbie Brooks. 1976 negotiations. [folder 2 of 3], 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Bobbie Brooks. 1976 negotiations. [folder 3 of 3], 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Bobbie Brooks. Colebrook Mills subsidiary., 1976 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  9/76. Issue of severance of Colebrook dye house from multi-plant bargaining unit.
- Bobbie Brooks. Hialeah Knitting Mills 1974 negotiations. [folder 1 of 2], 1973-1977 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  7/73-2/77.
- Bobbie Brooks. Hialeah Knitting Mills 1974 negotiations. [folder 2 of 2], 1973-1977 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Bobbie Brooks. Brooks Transportation 1974 negotiations., 1973-1977 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  4/73-2/77.
- Boston agreements., 1951-1954 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  1/51-3/54.
- Boston Apparel Guild agreements., 1967-1973 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Boston Dress and Sportswear negotiations., 1966-1972 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  12/66-6/72.
- Cloak-Out-of-Town agreement., 1955-1956 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  10/55-7/56.
- Cotton Dress agreement., 1956-1960 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  3/56-1/60.
- Country Miss negotiations. [folder 1 of 3], 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  4/73-5/74.
- Country Miss negotiations. [folder 2 of 3], 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 15)
- Country Miss negotiations. [folder 3 of 3], 1973-1974 (Box 36, Folder 16)
- Dressmakers' Joint Council. 1976 negotiations with Affiliated Dress Manufacturers, Inc., National Dress Manufacturers' Association, Inc., and Popular Priced Dress Manufacturers' Group, Inc., 1975-1976 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  10/75-1/76.
- Dressmakers' Joint Council. 1976 negotiations with Affiliated Dress Manufacturers, Inc., National Dress Manufacturers' Association, Inc., and Popular Priced Dress Manufacturers' Group, Inc. (Box 36, Folder 18)
  1/76-2/76.
- Dressmakers' Joint Council. 1976 negotiations with Affiliated Dress Manufacturers, Inc., National Dress Manufacturers' Association, Inc., and Popular Priced Dress Manufacturers' Group, Inc. (Box 36, Folder 19)
  2/76-3/76.
- Dressmakers' Joint Council. 1976 negotiations with Affiliated Dress Manufacturers, Inc., National Dress Manufacturers' Association, Inc., and Popular Priced Dress Manufacturers' Group, Inc. (Box 36, Folder 20)
- Dressmakers' Joint Council. 1976 negotiations with Affiliated Dress Manufacturers, Inc., National Dress Manufacturers' Association, Inc., and Popular Priced Dress Manufacturers' Group, Inc. (Box 36, Folder 21)
  3/76-4/76.
- Dressmakers' Joint Council. 1976 negotiations with Affiliated Dress Manufacturers, Inc., National Dress Manufacturers' Association, Inc., and Popular Priced Dress Manufacturers' Group, Inc., 1976-1979 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  4/76-3/79.
- Dressmakers' Joint Council. Proposed agreement by union and executed agreement., 1976-1979 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Transcript of Arbitration Between Apparel Manufacturer Association, Inc., Affiliated Dress Manufacturers Association, Inc., and Dressmakers' Joint Council., 1980 (Box 37, Folder 1a)
  5/80. 1 bound volume.
- Florida Apparel Manufacturers Association., 1956-1966 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  2/56-3/66.
- Florida standard agreement., 1956-1965 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  3/56-4/65.
- Greater Blouse, Skirt and Neckwear Contractors Association. Agreements. [folder 1 of 2], 1953-1978 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  Agreements of 1953, 1956, 1958, 1959, and 1978.
- Greater Blouse, Skirt and Neckwear Contractors Association. Agreements. [folder 2 of 2], 1953-1978 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Jonathan Logan. 1972 negotiations. [folder 1 of 2], 1971-1973 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  9/71-9/73.
- Jonathan Logan. 1972 negotiations. [folder 2 of 2], 1971-1973 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Kenrose Manufacturing Company. [folder 1 of 2], 1956-1963 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  3/56-2/63. Includes strike settlement, agreements on Ireland plant and severance pay.
- Kenrose Manufacturing Company. [folder 2 of 2], 1956-1963 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Local 25. [folder 1 of 3], 1953-1967 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  9/53-6/67. Agreements with Greater Blouse Contractors' Association, National Association of Blouse Manufacturers, and standard independents.
- Local 25. [folder 2 of 3], 1953-1967 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Local 25. [folder 2 of 3], 1953-1967 (Box 37, Folder 12)
- Mode O'Day. 1973 negotiations., 1973-1974 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  2/73-7/74.
- Needle Trades Employees Association., 1953 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  4/53.
- Needle Trades Employees Association., 1956-1958 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  2/56-5/58.
- Needle Trades Employees Association., 1958-1968 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  5/58-7/68.
- New England Apparel Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1956-1957 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  5/56-6/57.
- New England Apparel Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1957-1958 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  10/57-10/58.
- New England Apparel Manufacturers' Association, Inc., 1958-1959 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  10/58-4/59.
- E. Subject Files (Box 38)
  Deals with various aspects of union administration and internal affairs, especially with political finance, the Union Health Center and Unity House. Arranged in alphabetical order.
- New England Sportswear Manufacturers' Association., 1961-1965 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  5/61-2/65.
- New England Sportswear Manufacturers' Association., 1966-1968 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  4/66-5/68.
- New England Sportswear Manufacturers' Association., 1968-1973 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  5/68-12/73.
- Pennsylvania Dress Manufacturers' Association., 1945-1951 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  7/45-4/51.
- Pennsylvania Dress Manufacturers' Association., 1951-1955 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  4/51-2/55.
- Pennsylvania Dress Manufacturers' Association., 1955-1963 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  4/55-9/63.
- Popular Priced Dress Manufacturers Group, Inc., 1955 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  3/55. Agreement with United Popular Dress Manufacturers Association, Inc.
- Slate Belt Apparel Contractors' Association. 1950's negotiations and correspondence., 1950-1960 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  2/50-9/60.
- Slate Belt Apparel Contractors' Association. 1961-1962 negotiations and correspondence. (Box 38, Folder 9)
  9/61-10/62.
- Slate Belt Apparel Contractors' Association. 1964-1965 negotiations and correspondence. (Box 38, Folder 10)
  9/64-6/65.
- Slate Belt Apparel Contractors' Association. 1967 negotiations and correspondence., 1967-1969 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  6/67-5/69.
- Sportswear. 1976 negotiations correspondence., 1973-1976 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  6/73-3/76. Includes 1973 agreement.
- Sportswear. 1976 negotiations correspondence. (Box 38, Folder 13)
  4/76. Includes charts of various outerwear clauses.
- Sportswear. 1976 negotiations correspondence. (Box 38, Folder 14)
  4/76-5/76. Includes rough drafts of contract articles.
- Sportswear. 1976 negotiations correspondence. (Box 38, Folder 15)
  5/76-7/76. Includes 1976 blouse agreement.
- Sportswear. 1976 negotiations correspondence. (Box 38, Folder 16)
  7/76. Includes revision of drafts.
- Sportswear. 1976 negotiations correspondence. (Box 38, Folder 17)
  7/76-9/76. Includes proposed agreement.
- Sportswear. 1979 negotiations correspondence. (Box 38, Folder 18)
  3/79-10/79. Includes 1979 blouse agreement.
- Sportswear. 1979 negotiations correspondence. (Box 38, Folder 19)
  10/79. Includes 1979 sportswear agreement.
- St. Louis negotiations., 1954-1958 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  12/54-10/58.
- St. Louis negotiations., 1959-1960 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  11/59-2/60.
- United Popular Dress Manufacturers' Association., 1955-1958 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  3/55-7/58.
- Standard 1979 association agreement. (Box 38, Folder 23)
- David Dubinsky. Correspondence and bulletins., 1948-1957 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  2/48-6/57.
- David Dubinsky. Correspondence and bulletins., 1957-1958 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  7/57-8/58.
- David Dubinsky. Correspondence and bulletins., 1958-1970 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  10/58-3/70.
- Justice articles by Morris Glushien., 1954-1958 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  11/54-1/58.
- Labor Law Reform., 1977 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  1/77-7/77. Includes bills, correspondence, propaganda, and analyses on proposed labor law reform acts of 1977 and 1978.
- Labor Law Reform., 1977 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Labor Law Reform., 1977 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  7/77-8/77.
- Labor Law Reform., 1977 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  8/77-10/77.
- Labor Law Reform., 1977-1978 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  11/77-4/78.
- Labor Law Reform., 1978-1979 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  5/78-1/79.
- Liberal Party loan., 1961-1962 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  3/61-5/62.
- Merger with Insurance Workers., 1981 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  1/81. Includes letters and certificates of merger of Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (ACWA) and Textile Workers Union of America (TWUA) into Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union (ACTWU).
- Agreement and Plan of Merger and Consolidation, ACWA-TWUA, Exhibits A-D. (Box 39, Folder 12a)
- Agreement and Plan of Merger and Consolidation, ACWA-TWUA, Exhibits E-M. (Box 39, Folder 12b)
- Merger with Insurance Workers., 1981 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  1/81. Includes merger agreement between ACTWU and United Shoe Workers; and Insurance Workers' correspondence with Steel Workers.
- Minimum wage legislation. ILGWU's statements and positions., 1955 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  3/55-8/55.
- Political file. ILGWU 1970 Campaign Committee investigation., 1968-1971 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  2/68-6/71. Correspondence, memoranda, and minutes of meetings.
- Political file. ILGWU 1970 Campaign Committee investigation. [folder 1 of 5] (Box 39, Folder 16)
  Copies of checks and bank statements.
- Political file. ILGWU 1970 Campaign Committee investigation. [folder 2 of 5] (Box 39, Folder 17)
- Political file. ILGWU 1970 Campaign Committee investigation. [folder 3 of 5] (Box 39, Folder 18)
- Political file. ILGWU 1970 Campaign Committee investigation. [folder 4 of 5] (Box 39, Folder 19)
- Political file. ILGWU 1970 Campaign Committee investigation. [folder 5 of 5] (Box 39, Folder 20)
- Political file. Correspondence., 1970-1971 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  7/70-10/71. About suit against Paul Hall (president of Seafarers), and relevance to ILGWU Campaign Committee.
- Political file. Legal documents. [folder 1 of 3], 1970-1972 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  10/70-10/72. Relating to Pipefitters Local 562, Paul Hall, Tony Boyle (president of Mine Workers), federal law, and other cases.
- Political file. Legal documents. [folder 2 of 3], 1970-1972 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Political file. Legal documents. [folder 3 of 3], 1970-1972 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Political file. Copies of the Federal Register., 1970-1976 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  8/70-5/76.
- Political file. Correspondence., 1974 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  1/74-10/74. About various issues.
- Political file. Correspondence., 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  11/74-10/75. About various issues.
- Political file. Correspondence., 1976-1978 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  3/76-5/78. About various issues.
- Political file. Correspondence., 1978-1979 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  6/78-1/79. About various issues.
- Political file. Correspondence., 1979-1981 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  2/79-9/81. About various issues.
- Political file. Documents related to campaign finances., 1974-1979 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  5/74-8/79.
- Political file. 1976 Carter campaign. (Box 40, Folder 12)
  9/76-10/76.
- Political file. 1980 Carter campaign. (Box 40, Folder 13)
  3/80-10/80.
- Powell Committee. General Correspondence., 1962 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  4/62-7/62. Investigation of alleged discrimination by the ILGWU against blacks and Hispanics.
- Powell Committee. General Correspondence., 1962 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  8/62-9/62.
- Powell Committee. General Correspondence., 1962 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  9/62-12/62.
- Powell Committee. New York State Commission on Human Rights investigation of ILGWU discrimination against Ernest Holmes., 1962-1963 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  6/62-6/63.
- Powell Committee. No Negro Need Apply (television program on WNBC)., 1962 (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Powell Committee. Relevant materials., 1950-1960 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  U.S. Department of Labor document "Employment, Earnings and Wages in New York City, 1950-60."
- Powell Committee. Relevant materials. [folder 1 of 2], 1962 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  ILGWU internal documents. Includes GEB reports, financial reports, and daily proceedings of the 1962 convention.
- Powell Committee. Relevant materials. [folder 2 of 2], 1962 (Box 40, Folder 21)
- Powell Committee. Relevant materials. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 40, Folder 22)
  Cloak Joint Board (Murray Kolker. Administrative Secretary). Includes list of firms and contracts.
- Powell Committee. Relevant materials. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 40, Folder 23)
- Powell Committee. Relevant materials. (Box 40, Folder 24)
  Dress Joint Board (Charles Zimmerman. General Manager). Includes contract with Affiliated Dress Manufacturers.
- Powell Committee. Relevant materials. [folder 1 of 2] (Box 41, Folder 1)
  Rough list of firms and contracts of Local 10 (Moe Falikman. Manager).
- Powell Committee. Relevant materials. [folder 2 of 2] (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Powell Committee. Relevant materials. (Box 41, Folder 3)
  Rough list of firms and contracts of Local 25 (Charles Kreindler. Manager).
- Powell Committee. Relevant materials. (Box 41, Folder 4)
  Rough list of firms and contracts of Local 60-60A (William Schwartz. Manager).
- Powell Committee. Relevant materials. (Box 41, Folder 5)
  Rough list of firms and contracts of Local 89 (Salvatore Noto. Manager).
- Powell Committee. Relevant materials. [folder 1 of 3] (Box 41, Folder 6)
  Rough list of firms and contracts of Local 98 (Herbert Pokodner. Manager).
- Powell Committee. Relevant materials. [folder 2 of 3] (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Powell Committee. Relevant materials. [folder 3 of 3] (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Powell Committee. Relevant materials. (Box 41, Folder 9)
  Rough list of firms and contracts of Local 102 (Herbert Sherman. Manager).
- Powell Committee. Relevant materials. [folder 1 of 3] (Box 41, Folder 10)
  Rough list of firms and contracts of Local 105 (Martin L. Cohen. Manager).
- Powell Committee. Relevant materials. [folder 2 of 3] (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Powell Committee. Relevant materials. [folder 3 of 3] (Box 41, Folder 12)
- Hearings Before the Ad Hoc Subcommittee On Investigation of the Garment Industry., 1962 (Box 41, Folder 12a)
  8/62-9/62. 1 bound volume.
- Powell Committee. El Diario articles on discrimination in ILGWU shops., 1962 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  8/62.
- Powell Committee. Articles by Herbert Hill in New Politics., 1962 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  8/62-12/62?
- Powell Committee. Newspaper clippings. [folder 1 of 2], 1962-1963 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  7/62-2/63.
- Powell Committee. Newspaper clippings. [folder 2 of 2], 1962-1963 (Box 41, Folder 16)
- Racketeering newspaper clippings., 1958 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  6/58-7/58.
- Thompson Sub-committee on Labor of the House Committee on Education and Labor. Hearings on resistance to union organizing., 1967 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  4/67- 6/67.
- Thompson Sub-committee on Labor of the House Committee on Education and Labor. Hearings on resistance to union organizing., 1967 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  7/67- 8/67.
- Thompson Sub-committee on Labor of the House Committee on Education and Labor. Hearings on resistance to union organizing., 1967-1971 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  8/67-5/71.
- Thompson Sub-committee on Labor of the House Committee on Education and Labor. Oversight of National Labor Relations Board., 1975 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  1/75- 9/75.
- Thompson Sub-committee on Labor of the House Committee on Education and Labor. Oversight of National Labor Relations Board., 1975 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  10/75- 11/75.
- Thompson Sub-committee on Labor of the House Committee on Education and Labor. Oversight of National Labor Relations Board., 1976-1977 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  1/76-1/77.
- Union Health Center. Basement and leases., 1946-1959 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  9/46-2/59.
- Union Health Center. Government regulations. [folder 1 of 2], 1962-1973 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  9/62-10/73.
- Union Health Center. Government regulations. [folder 2 of 2], 1962-1973 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Union Health Center. Income tax exemption., 1946-1961 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  12/46-10/61.
- Union Health Center. Income tax exemption., 1962-1964 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  5/62-5/64.
- Union Health Center. Income tax exemption., 1964-1968 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  5/64-7/68.
- Union Health Center. Labor contracts. [folder 1 of 2], 1963-1974 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  10/63-10/74.
- Union Health Center. Labor contracts. [folder 2 of 2], 1963-1974 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Union Health Center. Lay staff arbitration., 1955-1975 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  12/55-7/75.
- Union Health Center. Malpractice law file. (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Union Health Center. Management matters., 1960-1976 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  9/60-8/76.
- Union Health Center. Medical staff correspondence and contracts., 1957-1971 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  6/57-8/71.
- Union Health Center. Mortgage extension on 275 7th Avenue., 1946-1967 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  2/46-9/67.
- Union Health Center. Mortgage payments on building. [folder 1 of 2], 1945-1971 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  9/45-10/71.
- Union Health Center. Mortgage payments on building. [folder 2 of 2], 1945-1971 (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Union Health Center. New York City and New York State sales tax exemptions., 1946-1965 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  8/46-10/65.
- Union Health Center. Nurses' Guild (Local 312 of Building Service Employees). Correspondence and contracts., 1954-1961 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  9/54-11/61.
- Union Health Center. Nurses' Guild (Local 312 of Building Service Employees). Correspondence and contracts., 1961-1966 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  11/61-2/66.
- Union Health Center. Nurses' Guild (Local 312 of Building Service Employees). Correspondence and contracts., 1966-1974 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  3/66-7/74.
- Union Health Center. Office Employees Local 153. Correspondence and contracts., 1965-1973 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  8/65-12/73.
- Union Health Center. Pharmacy regulations correspondence., 1962-1971 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  1/62-12/71.
- Union Health Center. Dr. Leo Price (former director). Correspondence., 1949-1960 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  1/49-7/60.
- Union Health Center. Property damage insurance claims on 275 7th Avenue. [folder 1 of 2], 1949-1973 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  11/49-7/73.
- Union Health Center. Property damage insurance claims on 275 7th Avenue. [folder 2 of 2], 1949-1973 (Box 42, Folder 24)
- Union Health Center. Real estate tax file., 1948-1962 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  8/48-1/62. Includes correspondence about exemptions and dealings with the City of New York Tax Commission.
- Union Health Center. Real estate tax file., 1962-1964 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  2/62-12/64.
- Union Health Center. Real estate tax file., 1965-1972 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  2/65-7/72.
- Union Health Center. Real estate tax file., 1972-1976 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  10/72-10/76.
- Union Health Center. Staff matters., 1972-1975 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  8/72-4/75.
- Union Health Center. Staff retirement fund., 1958-1961 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  5/58-1/61. Includes initial proposals, actuarial and financial analyses, correspondence.
- Union Health Center. Staff retirement fund., 1961-1966 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  1/61-1/66.
- Union Health Center. Staff retirement fund., 1966-1972 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  2/66-12/72.
- Union Health Center. Tax shelter annuity plan with Hartford Life Insurance Company., 1974-1975 (Box 43, Folder 9)